Hello.
こんにちは
It's tall.
背高いですね
My legs are long.
足長いし
The uniform suits her better than I imagined.
想像以上に制服が似合いすぎるんです
I'm excited though.
興奮してるんですけど
It's been a while since I've been here.
久しぶりに来ました
That's cool, now you have twin tails.
やばいね、これでツインテールを
Please tell me your name.
ちょっとお名前を
It's M.
Mです
Mr. M.
Mさん
Isn't it a little creepy?
ちょっとキモいですかね
You're breathing hard.
鼻息が荒いですね
Please sit down for a moment.
ちょっと 座っていただいて
What about your school days?
学生時代どうですか?
Have you ever had sex like this?
こういうのエッチしたことあります?
In uniform.
制服で
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張してますか?
I'm really nervous.
めちゃめちゃ緊張してます
I'm still not used to it.
まだ慣れないですね
We'll have sex again in a bright place today.
今日また明るい場所でエッチしますけど
It's so bright.
めちゃめちゃ明るいです
Do you know what I'm going to do today?
今日これから何してるか分かります?
I don't know.
分からないです
With my uncle.
おじさんと
Do you want to have sex?
エッチしますか?
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
There
そこ
Roll up your pants.
で パンツを巻く
Wrap the skirt.
スカートを巻く
Aren't you an idol or something?
近アイドルとかやってないんだ?
I haven't done it.
やってない
Looks good, doesn't it?
いそうだよね
lie?
うそ?
I'm here.
いるいる
Wrap the skirt.
スカートを巻く
Like Tief.
ティーフのみたいな
Wrap your butt too.
お尻も巻く
You can get on all fours.
四つんばになってもいい
Wrap the skirt too.
スカートも巻く
vinegar
ス
Roll up the cart.
カ ートを巻く
First like this.
まずこのように
Will it come out?
抜けるかな?
Should I hide it a little?
ちょっと隠すか?
Can I cover it with my hands?
手で隠していい?
Can I spread it out?
広げてもらっていい?
Cut with both hands?
両手で切る?
Together.
一緒にね
It's a little more analog.
もうちょっとアナログしますね
Can I mess things up a bit?
ちょっと雑らしていいですか?
yes.
はい
Is it a bit boring?
ちょっとカンボツチクビ?
It's changed.
変わっちゃった
I like the slightly reluctant look on his face.
ちょっと嫌がる顔がいいですね
It has a special feel.
特感があります
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Vibration is better.
振動のほうがいいんだよ
My chestnut is poky.
クリがポッキーしてる
Feels good.
気持ちいい
My chestnut is poky
クリがポッキーして
Ru.
る
What about chestnuts?
ク リはどうに?
Which one feels better?
ど っち が気持ちいい?
I also like chestnuts.
クリも好き
ク リも好き
Can you see your own clit?
自分のクリを見える?
appear.
見える
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You've got a tail.
お前に尻尾が出てきちゃった
So let's shake it up ourselves.
じゃあちょっと自分で振りやしましょう
amazing...
すごい...
Uncle Chijin
おじさんチジン
It was.
た ね
You've got a tail.
お前に尻尾が出てきちゃった
So let's shake it up ourselves.
じゃあちょっと自分で振りよう
Go and try it.
行ってみて
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
amazing.
すごい
Can I come in?
入 るかな?
Uncle Governor, that's about it.
おじさん知事、これぐらいだからさ
Well then, please go slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり行ってみてね
Did you like it?
気に入った?
this.
これ
You'll become stronger.
強くなるんだ
That's about it.
これぐらいだからさ
Well then, please go slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり行ってみてね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did you see it?
見えた?
this.
これ
You'll become stronger.
強くなるんだ
It's coming to my finger.
指にくるじゃん
What are you doing with your fingers?
指を何にしてない?
Toys.
おもちゃに
It can be pushed out into the hand.
手に押し出せる
Okay, listen.
よし、いいか
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
I'll check the complaints.
文句チェックしますね
It's delicious.
うまいね
What do you think, Chin-Chin?
どうですか、ちんちん?
big.
大きい
hard?
硬い?
Looks like fun.
楽しそうですね
soft.
柔らかい
Are you doing well there?
そこでしっかりしてる?
Yeah.
うん
slippery.
つるつる
Come on up a little.
ちょっとカモンジング上げてきて
Bring on the cumming.
カモンジング上げてきて
picture?
え?
Okay?
いいかい?
Yeah.
うん
Come on up a little.
ちょっとカモンジング上げてきて
picture?
え?
Okay?
いいかい?
Yeah.
うん
horse
う ま
stomach.
い
I'll give you some.
ちょっと あげる
I'll give it to you.
あっちにあげる
Yeah.
うん
It's going to move.
動いちゃう
It moves a lot.
めっちゃ動く
It seems likely.
ありそう
Yeah.
うん
Let's move
動いちゃ
cormorant.
う
It moves a lot.
め っちゃ動く
Kino
き の
Chan, I'll add matchin.
ちゃん、 マッチンコ入れますね
Which feels better, chin chin or gilt?
チンチンとギルト、どっちが気持ちいい?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
thank you.
ありがとう
I can hold my feet.
足を押さえられる自分で
It's a mess though.
くちゃくちゃなんだけど
It's easy to apply.
塗りやすいんだ
Easy to apply.
塗りやすい
It feels good.
気持ちいいと
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Do you feel good?
気 持 ちいい?
Can I put it in?
入れていいんですか?
That's fine.
いいですよ
You can sleep.
寝ていいよ
Are you sleeping?
寝てるかな?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Just touch me.
ちょっと触って
Are you sleeping?
寝てる?
I'm sleeping.
寝てる
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
Can I cum inside you?
中出していい?
yes.
はい
I'm sleeping.
寝てるよ
I'm going to sleep.
寝るね
Open it.
開いて
I slept a lot, so can I touch you?
いっぱい寝たんで、触ってもらっていいですか?
It fell down.
下に垂れちゃったもんね
Oh no.
いやぁ
I've been out so much that my health has been suffering.
こんだけ外出たから、体調が困られてきた
Well, now that I've had a good night's sleep, let's go wash up.
じゃあ、いっぱい寝たんで、洗っていかりましょう
It's refreshing.
爽やかですね
That's amazing.
すごいよ